Guide to the Fashion Moda Archive 1978-1993 MSS 091
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series III: Artists, Exhibitions, and related material
  - Subseries E: Printed Materials
    - Kostabi, Mark: catalog, 1986. (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Mati et Mire, Isy Brachot, Paris: 1985. (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Mickiemoda, Annie: "The Modamutations"., undated (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - New Observations, issue #71, October 1 - November 14, 1989. (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - New Observations, issue #73, January 1 - February 14, 1990. (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - New Observation, issue #75, April 1 - May 14, 1990. (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Pflasterstrand, vom 31. 1 bis 13. 2. 1981, Germany. (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Rammellzee: "Iconic Treatise Gothic Futurism... ", 1979 (Box 6, Folder 16A.)
    - Space Window, catalog, September 14 - October 6, 1997. (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Stout, Nancy: "The Way We Were"., undated (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Unidentified printed materials., undated (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Virus, graffiti zine, Holland., undated (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Waxberg, Richard, undated (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Yarber, Robert, undated (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Subseries F[1]: Slides
    Box 7: 1978 - 1980
    - [item removed], undated (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Hill-Montgomery, Candance: installation, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - [item removed], undated (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Polly Ester Nation: "Jesus Comes to the Bronx", March 1980. (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - May 1980. (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Steinbach, Haim: Summer 1980. (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Edwards, Marianne: Summer 1980. (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Dickson, Jane: "City Maze", September 6 - October 4, 1980. (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Sophie Calle, C. Ginsberg, November 25, 1980. (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Cooper, Martha: Subwa, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Subseries F[2]: Slides
    Box 8: 1981 - 1983
    - Eyes and Ears Foundation, "California Billboards", 1980- 1981 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - California Billboards in New York, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 11A)
    - Pass, D.: "It's a Piece of Cake", 1980- 1981 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Yohai Andors, Rhoda: "Skeleton Paintings", February 6-28, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Optima Studio: New Orleans, Spring, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Pizzanello, Josephine, others, Fall 1981 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Graffiti: Summer 1981. (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Contemporary Art Center, New Orleans: Summer 1981. (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - South Bronx Art, Projects, Others: Summer 1981. (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - de Mille, Arnette / Malca: Dance at opening of "South Bronx Art, Projects, Others", Summer 1981 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Larkin, Sara: "Scapes of Outer Space", September 1981. (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - October 1981. (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Pou, Alyson: "Measured Fantasies", November 1981. (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Thomas, Kathleen: Fall 1981. (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Wells, David: "Royal Hunt" and "Time Machine", Fall 1981. (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Gutzeit, Fred: January 16 - February 17, 1982. (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Spring Fever, March 1982 (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Documenta 7: merchandise, May 1982. [No Duplication Allowed] (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - South Bronx Show, Summer 1982. (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - Baca, Fred, Fekner, John and Leicht, Don: "From Monkey to Monitor", Fall 1982. (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - Graffiti Mural, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - Haring, Keith: "Installation at Tony Shafrazi", 1983 (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - Golubovic, Vesna: Installation on E 146 St, Bronx, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 32)
    - Dragan Ilic: "Man with the Red Pencils", February 1983. (Box 8, Folder 33)
    - Seeno, Anson: "Watching", March 1983. (Box 8, Folder 34)
    - Fashion Moda Open House, July 23, 1983. (Box 8, Folder 35)
    - Pier 34, exhibition, Fall 1983. (Box 8, Folder 35a.)
    - Rheinberg, Raffael: September 1983. (Box 8, Folder 36)
    - Roloff, Stephen: "Paper Murals", September 25, 1983. (Box 8, Folder 37)
    - Collins, Marshall: "World of Dinosaurs", November - December 1983. (Box 8, Folder 38)
    - Daze, Keith Haring, Kenny Scharf, others: Mural at Houston and Bowery, NYC, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 38A)
  - Subseries F[3]: Slides
    Box 9: 1984
    - Touring Show, "Of the Streets", 1984 [see also I. 1. 34 and III. C. 6. 6 and III. B. oversize 21. 19-24] (Box 9, Folder 39)
    - Poppitz, James: tour and projects, 1983-1986 (Box 9, Folder 40)
    - Wahl, Anita: January 10 - February 8, 1984. (Box 9, Folder 41)
    - [item removed]., undated (Box 9, Folder 42)
    - Buggiani, Paolo: April 7-17, 1984. (Box 9, Folder 43)
    - Graupe-Pill, Grace:, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 44)
    - Cyphers, Peggy: "Modern Fossils", April 28, 1984. (Box 9, Folder 45)
    - Graffiti Masters Show: April 28 - May 19, 1984. (Box 9, Folder 46)
    - Niedzialek, Terry: July 1984. (Box 9, Folder 47)
    - South Bronx Show: August 1984. (Box 9, Folder 48)
    - South Bronx, ca. 1984 (Box 9, Folder 48A.)
    - Mulero, Lillian: "Real Politic", October 29 - November 16, 1984. (Box 9, Folder 49)
    - Lady Pink/Lady Heart: installation, November 1984. (Box 9, Folder 50)
    - Ellis, Darrel: "Drawings from my Father's Photographs", December 1984. (Box 9, Folder 51)
    - Edwards, Marianne:, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 52)
  - Subseries F[4]: Slides
    Box 10: 1985
    - A-One, Toxic, Koor:, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 53)
    - P. S. 25: March, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 54)
    - Van II: March, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 55)
    - Chaiklin, Amy: March 9 - April 10, 1985. (Box 10, Folder 56)
    - Social Studies, Agent, Marc Brasz & James Rivera: April 20 - May 16, 1985. (Box 10, Folder 57)
    - Democracy at Work at 22 Wooster St.: May 31 - June 22, 1985. (Box 10, Folder 58)
    - Poppitz, James: Graffiti Desk at Fashion Moda, June 1985 [see also I. 1. 32]. (Box 10, Folder 59)
    - South Bronx Show: June 15 - July 17, 1985. (Box 10, Folder 60)
    - Fiorucci: window displays, July 19 - August 1, 1985. (Box 10, Folder 61)
    - Expression African, September 1985. (Box 10, Folder 62)
    - Eins, Stefan: November 1985. (Box 10, Folder 63)
    - Fashion Moda Benefit at Ronald Feldman, Soho, November 1-16, 1985. (Box 10, Folder 64)
    - Intentionally omitted, undated (Box 10, Folder 65)
  - Subseries F[5]: Slides
    Box 11: 1985 - 1986
    - [item removed], undated (Box 11, Folder 66)
    - Robert Grahm/Susan Springfield: December 1985 - January 1986., 1985 - 1986 (Box 11, Folder 67)
    - Tim Rollins and the Kids of Survival: January - February 1986. (Box 11, Folder 68)
    - Stout, Nancy: march 1986. (Box 11, Folder 69)
    - Pod: facade of Fashion Moda, March 1986 [see also I. 1. 40] (Box 11, Folder 70)
    - Sacchetto, Bruce: March 1 - April 12, 1986. (Box 11, Folder 71)
    - Images in Fiber & Cloth: April 1986. (Box 11, Folder 72)
    - Lowinger, Leslie: May 7, 1986. (Box 11, Folder 73)
    - Moet and Delta: facade of Fashion Moda, June - July 1986. [see also I. 1. 40] (Box 11, Folder 74)
    - South Bronx Show: June 21 - August 1, 1986. (Box 11, Folder 75)
    - Pieces Sold: June 1986. (Box 11, Folder 76)
    - [item removed], undated (Box 11, Folder 77)
    - Art for Money Benefit, December 1986 (Box 11, Folder 78)
    - Police Officers from local precinct: Installation, n. d., undated (Box 11, Folder 78A)
  - Subseries F[6]: Slides
    Box 12: 1987 - 1993
    - Unidentified, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 79)
    - Unidentified exhibition, July 1987. (Box 12, Folder 80)
    - South Bronx Show: 1987. (Box 12, Folder 81)
    - [item removed], undated (Box 12, Folder 82)
    - Corn, Thom: 1988. (Box 12, Folder 83)
    - Wibmer, Margret; March 29 - April 15, 1988. (Box 12, Folder 84)
    - Lens, Jessica: "The Sun, the Moon, and the Connected Stars... ", June 15-28, 1988. (Box 12, Folder 85)
    - Smith, Barbara: "Pageant of the Holy Squash", December 1988. (Box 12, Folder 86)
    - Back Room: January 1989. (Box 12, Folder 87)
    - New location: January 1989 (Box 12, Folder 87A)
    - Toral, Tabo: facade of Fashion Moda, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 88)
    - Misera, Lisi: Installation, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 88A)
    - Unidentified Slides, undated (Box 12, Folder 91)
  - Subseries F[7]: Slides
    Box 13: Individual Artists A-K.
    - Ahearn, John, undated (Box 13, Folder 92)
    - Anderson, Laurie., undated (Box 13, Folder 93)
    - Applebroog, Ida., undated (Box 13, Folder 94)
    - Beuys, Joseph, undated (Box 13, Folder 94A.)
    - Bieber, Lorna., undated (Box 13, Folder 95)
    - Brasz, Mark, undated (Box 13, Folder 96)
    - Brown, Marion., undated (Box 13, Folder 97)
    - Buggiani, Paolo, undated (Box 13, Folder 97A)
    - Chaiklin, Amy., undated (Box 13, Folder 98)
    - Charles, Andre., undated (Box 13, Folder 99)
    - Cohen, Helen., undated (Box 13, Folder 100)
    - Colescott, Robert., undated (Box 13, Folder 101)
    - Collins, Marshall, undated (Box 13, Folder 101A.)
    - Corn, Thom., undated (Box 13, Folder 102)
    - Crash., undated (Box 13, Folder 103)
    - Crawford, Lonnie & Cutrone., undated (Box 13, Folder 104)
    - Daze., undated (Box 13, Folder 105)
    - de Preter, Jon., undated (Box 13, Folder 106)
    - Dickson, Jane., undated (Box 13, Folder 107)
    - Drew, Nancy, undated (Box 13, Folder 107A.)
    - Eins, Stefan., undated (Box 13, Folder 108)
    - English, Ron., undated (Box 13, Folder 109)
    - [item removed]., undated (Box 13, Folder 110)
    - Fekner, John., undated (Box 13, Folder 111)
    - Finn, David., undated (Box 13, Folder 112)
    - Freedom, undated (Box 13, Folder 112A.)
    - Fun shots of Fashion Moda., undated (Box 13, Folder 113)
    - Futura 2000, undated (Box 13, Folder 113A)
    - Gadea, Patricia., undated (Box 13, Folder 114)
    - Hambleton, Richard., undated (Box 13, Folder 115)
    - Haring, Keith., undated (Box 13, Folder 116)
    - Harris, Tim., undated (Box 13, Folder 117)
    - Headley, Wendell., undated (Box 13, Folder 118)
    - Hertz, Betti-Sue., undated (Box 13, Folder 119)
    - Hill-Montgomery, Candace., undated (Box 13, Folder 120)
    - Hoffman, Wendy., undated (Box 13, Folder 121)
    - Ilic, Dragan, undated (Box 13, Folder 121A.)
    - Jordan, Ariel Orr., undated (Box 13, Folder 122)
    - Jones, Kim, undated (Box 13, Folder 123)
    - Kostabi, Mark., undated (Box 13, Folder 124)
    - Ladda, Justen., undated (Box 13, Folder 124A.)
  - Subseries F[8]: Slides
    Box 14: Individual Artists L-Z
    - Quinones, Lee, undated (Box 14, Folder 125)
    - Lewis, Joe., undated (Box 14, Folder 126)
    - Lowinger, Leslie., undated (Box 14, Folder 127)
    - Mann, Frank, undated (Box 14, Folder 127A.)
    - Nadel, Jeremy., undated (Box 14, Folder 128)
    - Neal, Willie, undated (Box 14, Folder 128A.)
    - Paddock, Laura, undated (Box 14, Folder 129)
    - Pink, Lady, undated (Box 14, Folder 129A.)
    - Quinn, Barbara., undated (Box 14, Folder 130)
    - Reccha, Lewis., undated (Box 14, Folder 131)
    - Rivera, James., undated (Box 14, Folder 132)
    - Rifka, Judy, undated (Box 14, Folder 132A.)
    - Roloff, Stephan., undated (Box 14, Folder 133)
    - Rothchild, Gail., undated (Box 14, Folder 134)
    - Schlefer, R., undated (Box 14, Folder 135)
    - Schwartz, Steve, undated (Box 14, Folder 136)
    - Seeno, Anson, undated (Box 14, Folder 136A.)
    - Smith, Mary Agnes, undated (Box 14, Folder 136B.)
    - Spero, Nancy., undated (Box 14, Folder 137)
    - Steckel, Anita, undated (Box 14, Folder 137A.)
    - Strauss, Sandy., undated (Box 14, Folder 138)
    - Street Art, undated (Box 14, Folder 138A.)
    - Spank., undated (Box 14, Folder 139)
    - Sumner, Holly & Talbot, Nina., undated (Box 14, Folder 140)
    - Toral, Tabo., undated (Box 14, Folder 141)
    - Transue, Michael., undated (Box 14, Folder 141A.)
    - Tuck, Norman., undated (Box 14, Folder 142)
    - Unidentified artists, undated (Box 14, Folder 143)
    - Various., undated (Box 14, Folder 143A)
    - Warren, Tom, undated (Box 14, Folder 144)
    - Weeks, Lionel "Agent", undated (Box 14, Folder 145)
    - Wodiczko, Krysztof., undated (Box 14, Folder 146)
    - Wosk, Miriam., undated (Box 14, Folder 147)
    - undated (Box 14, Folder .)
  - Subseries F[9]: Slides
    Box 15: Slide Presentation
    - Fashion Moda Slide Show: with explanation sheet (ca 1990), an introductory overview, including certain duplicates (Box 15, Folder 148)
  - Subseries G: Video - Access Copies
    Consists of VHS access copies for Stephan Eins' Making Coincidences and other cable TV programs. Access copies are listed chronologically.
    - Cable TV 1 - Josef, circa mid-1970s (Shelf Media, Media ID: 091.0071)
      Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements note
      1/2" VHS videocassette. TRT: 00:29:00.
    - Cable TV 2 - Leanne, circa mid-1970s (Shelf Media, Media ID: 091.0073)
    - Cable TV 3 - Terry & Wendy, circa mid-1970s (Shelf Media, Media ID: 091.0075)
    - Cable TV 4 - Alone, circa mid-1970s (Shelf Media, Media ID: 091.0078)
      Format: DVD
      TRT: 00:29:00
    - "Grafitti" Dub; CBS "30-Minutes", undated (Shelf Media, Media ID: 091.0081)
      TRT: 00:14:00
    - Making Coincidences, February 5, 1984. (Shelf Media, Media ID: 091.0033)
    - Making Coincidences, February 12, 1984 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 091.0035)
    - Making Coincidences, February 19, 1984 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 091.0037)
      1/2" VHS videocassette. TRT: 00:30:00.
    - Making Coincidences, February 26, 1984 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 091.0039)
    - Making Coincidences, March 4, 1984 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 091.0041)
    - Making Coincidences, March 18, 1984 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 091.0043)
    - Making Coincidences, March 25, 1984 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 091.0045)
    - Making Coincidences, April 1, 1984 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 091.0047)
    - Making Coincidences, April 8, 1984 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 091.0049)
      1/2" VHS videocassette. TRT: 00:28:00.
    - Making Coincidences, April 15, 1984 (as per cassette)/April 22, 1984 (as per container) (Shelf Media, Media ID: 091.0051)
    - Making Coincidences, April 29 & May 6, 1984 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 091.0053)
    - Making Coincidences, May 13, 1984 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 091.0055)
    - Making Coincidences, May 27, 1984 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 091.0057)
    - Making Coincidences, May 27, 1984 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 091.0059)
      1/2" VHS videocassette. TRT: 00:07:00.
    - Making Coincidences, June 3, 1984 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 091.0061)
    - Making Coincidences, X. Y. C., 1984 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 091.0063)
    - Slow Scan: March, 1979 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 091.0084)
      TRT" 00:22:00
    - Stefan Eins Presents: July 11 and 21, 1986 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 091.0065)
    - Stefan Eins Presents: 2/25/1987 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 091.0067)
      1/2" VHS videocassette. TRT: 00:47:00.
    - Stefan Eins Presents: edit in process, March 25, 1987 (Shelf Media, Media ID: 091.0069)
  - Subseries H: Video - Originals
    Consists of original source tapes for Stephan Eins' Making Coincidences and other cable TV programs. Materials are listed chronologically. For access copies please see Subseries G.
    - Press for Making Coincidences, title cards for show. [see also oversize, box 21], undated (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Cable TV-1-Josef, n. d., circa mid-1970s (Folder ID: 091.0021)
      3/4" Umatic videocassette. Tape length 30 minutes.
    - Cable TV -2-Leanne, n. d., circa mid-1970s (Folder ID: 091.0022)
    - Cable TV -3-Terry & Wendy, n. d., circa mid-1970s (Folder ID: 091.0023)
    - Cable TV -4-Alone, n. d., circa mid-1970s (Folder ID: 091.0024)
    - [1.] -- Slow Scan Tele Conference [2.] -- Manhattan/Bronx; 3/6/1979 and 3/7/1979. (Folder ID: 091.0029)
      3/4" Umatic videocassette. Tape length 20 minutes.
    - Fashion Moda Documentary, July 4, 1982. (Folder ID: 091.0026)
      1/2" VHS videocassette PAL. Tape length 120 minutes.
    - Making Coincidences, February 5, 1984. (Folder ID: 091.0001)
    - Making Coincidences, February 12, 1984. (Folder ID: 091.0002)
    - Making Coincidences, February 19, 1984. (Folder ID: 091.0003)
    - Making Coincidences, February 26, 1984. (Folder ID: 091.0004)
    - Making Coincidences, March 4, 1984. (Folder ID: 091.0005)
    - Making Coincidences, March 18, 1984. (Folder ID: 091.0006)
    - Making Coincidences, March 25, 1984. (Folder ID: 091.0007)
    - Making Coincidences, April 1, 1984. (Folder ID: 091.0008)
    - Making Coincidences, April 8, 1984. (Folder ID: 091.0009)
    - Making Coincidences, April 15, 1984 (as per cassette)/April 22, 1984 (as per container). (Folder ID: 091.0010)
    - Making Coincidences, April 29 & May 6, 1984. (Folder ID: 091.0011)
    - Making Coincidences, May 13, 1984. (Folder ID: 091.0012)
    - Making Coincidences, May 27, 1984. (Folder ID: 091.0013)
    - Making Coincidences, May 27, 1984. (Folder ID: 091.0014)
    - Making Coincidences, June 3, 1984. (Folder ID: 091.0015)
    - Making Coincidences, X. Y. C., n. d.., 1984 (Folder ID: 091.0016)
    - Stefan Eins Presents: July 11 and 21, 1986. (Folder ID: 091.0017)
    - Stefan Eins Presents: 2/25/1987. (Folder ID: 091.0018)
    - Stefan Eins Presents: edit in process, March 25, 1987. (Folder ID: 091.0019)
    - Commercials for Stefan, n. d., 1987 (Folder ID: 091.0020)
    - Colab extinction, n. d., undated (Folder ID: 091.0025)
      Betamax
    - Fashion Moda Gallery- South Bronx, tape 1., undated (Folder ID: 091.0027)
    - Graffiti., undated (Folder ID: 091.0028)
    - Barbara Smith Fashion Moda Request E., undated (Folder ID: 091.0030)
      1/2" VHS videocassette PAL. Tape length 30 minutes.
    - Unidentified video tape., undated (Folder ID: 091.0031)
- Oversize: Series I: Fashion Moda Overview
  - Subseries B: Chronological
    - Gilded ornament from Satanic Sisters event [see also I.B.1.21], undated (Box 23)
- Oversize: Series II: Fashion Moda as a Business
  - Subseries A: Administrative Files
    - Ongoing renovations., undated (Box 20, Folder 64)
- Oversize: Series III: Artists, Exhibitions, and Related Materials
  - Subseries A: Artist Files
    - Program Report., undated (Box 20, Folder 90)
    - Science, Invention, Technology, Art and Fantasy, images used for first exhibition, 1978 [see also I. 1. 7A] (Box 20, Folder 7AA)
    - "Science, Invention, Technology, Art and Fantasy", production material 1978 [see also I. 1. 7A] (Box 20, Folder 7AB)
    - Designs for Documenta 7 t-shirts, 1982. [No Duplication Allowed] (Box 21, Folder 32a)
    - Holzer, Jenny: "Truisms", for Documenta 7, 1982.[No Duplication Allowed] (Box 21, Folder 32b)
    - Production Materials for Documenta 7 Store, 1982.[No Duplication Allowed] (Box 21, Folder 32c)
    - Production Materials for Documenta 7, transparencies. [No Duplication Allowed], undated (Box 21, Folder 32d)
    - Science, Art, Design, Invention, Technology, Fantasy, a brochure, 1984 [see also III. A. 5. 109 and III. A. oversize box 21. 114] (Box 21, Folder 114)
  - Oversize: Series III, Subseries B: Exhibition Promotion.
    - Flyers and Posters, 1979- 1981 (Box 21, Folder 14-18)
    - Flyers and Posters, 1983- 1988 (Box 21, Folder 19-23)
    - Flyers and Posters, 1989- 1993 (Box 21, Folder 25)
    - Flyers and Posters, n. d., undated (Box 21, Folder 26)
    - Articles on Fashion Moda, 1981 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Articles on Fashion Moda, n. d., undated (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Announcements from other galleries., undated (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - Oversize: Series III, Subseries C: Photographs.
    - Eins, Stefan, Jones, Baird & Mark Kostabi, 1985- 1986 (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - Oversize: Series III, Subseries D: Artworks.
    - Aone, painting. (tag) [No Duplication Allowed], undated (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Crash, painting. (tag) [No Duplication Allowed], undated (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Eins, Stefan: painting. (tag), undated (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Fekner, John: drawing for Documenta 7. [No Duplication Allowed], undated (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Haring, Keith: drawing for Documenta 7.[No Duplication Allowed], undated (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Mullican Matt: poster, undated (Box 21, Folder 13B)
    - Nenner, Paulette: drawing. [No Duplication Allowed], undated (Box 21, Folder 14: 00)
    - Pou, Alyson: collage. [No Duplication Allowed], undated (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - Scharf, Kenny: drawings for Documenta 7.[No Duplication Allowed], undated (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - Toxic, drawing. (tag), undated (Box 21, Folder 22)
    - G-Man, Tag, undated (Box 21, Folder 23)
    - van Dalen, Anton: drawing for Documenta 7 [No Duplication Allowed], undated (Box 21, Folder 23A)
    - Wells, David: drawing for Documenta 7. [No Duplication Allowed], undated (Box 21, Folder 24)
    - Y-Pants, drawing, undated (Box 21, Folder 25)
    - unidentified drawing, undated (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - Oversize: Series III, Subseries H: Video - Originals
    Subseries H: Video - Originals
    - Making Coincidences, title cards., undated (Box 21, Folder 1)
- Over-Oversize: Series I: Fashion Moda Overview
  - Cooney, Robert "Por Exxon, for Kill", painting., undated (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Eins, Stefan "Billiard/Pool for Random Objects", instructions., undated (Box 22, Folder 20)
- Over-Oversize: Series III, Subseries A: Administrative Files.
  - Subseries A: Administrative Files
    - Eins, Stefan: poster., undated (Box 22, Folder 37A)
    - Evans, Andrea: proposal., undated (Box 22, Folder 43)
  - Subseries B: Grants and Fundraising
    - flyers and poster, 1983-1987 (Box 22, Folder 19-23)
  - Subseries D: Artworks
    - Kostner, Arthur: two drawings., undated (Box 22, Folder 13a)
    - Fashion Moda Portfolio., undated (Box Map case, Folder 26)